Guide to the Roth and Moore Architects Records Concerning the Seeley G. Mudd Library, Yale University
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Roth and Moore Architects records concerning the Seeley G. Mudd Library, Yale University
1977-1986
RU 1019
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
6.0
(7 boxes)
The records consist of memoranda, correspondence, notes, drawings, specifications, and awards documenting Roth and Moore Architects' design and construction of the Seeley G. Mudd Library, Yale University.
Roth and Moore Architects
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-B (YRG 46-B), Records and materials documenting individual Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were a gift of Roth and Moore Architects, 2006; awards transferred from Yale Seeley G. Mudd Library, 2015.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession, and thereunder alphabetically by topic and material type.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of memoranda, correspondence, notes, drawings, specifications, and awards documenting Roth and Moore Architects' design and construction of the Seeley G. Mudd Library, Yale University.
Academic libraries -- Design and construction; College buildings -- Design and construction; Architectural drawings (visual works); Architectural records; Roth and Moore Architects; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University. Library
- Records documenting design and construction of Seeley G. Mudd Library, Yale University Library, by Roth and Moore Architects, 1977-1986; Accession 2007-A-091
  - Administration, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bulletins and sketches, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2 - 3)
  - Electrical submissions, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4 - 5)
  - HVAC submissions, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 6 - 7)
  - Items on hold/pending, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lighting submissions, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Materials, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Plumbing submissions, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Price requests/change orders, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Publicity, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13 - 16)
  - Punch lists, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Shop drawings, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 18 - 19)
  - Shop drawings, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 20 - 21)
  - Specs, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Stacks info, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Yale Library Annex - Clovis, 1977-1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Yale book storage - notes, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Yale Storage Library, Circa 1971 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Construction records
    - Preliminary work, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 27 - 31)
    - Test reports, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 32 - 35)
    - Shop drawings, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Day-to-day documentation
      - 1980 Oct-1981 February (Box 3, Folder 37 - 42)
      - 1981 March-1982 February (Box 4, Folder 43-56)
      - 1982 March-1986 August (Box 5, Folder 57-68)
- Awards for the design of the Seeley G. Mudd Library, 1983; Accession 2015-A-060
  - CRSI Design Awards Program VII, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Connecticut Society of Architects/American Institute of Architects design awards, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - American Institute of Architects award of excellence, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Concrete Building Award of merit, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)